Guide to the Frank M. Ingalls Photograph Collection ca. 1901-1930 PR 28
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Photographic prints
  - Subseries I.1: Individually cataloged prints (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1, Box-folder 1)
    - 164a, Mr. Eddie Dorie on stilts, Broadway and Morris Street, cafeteria sign (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 164b, Mr. Eddie Dorie on stilts, Broadway and Morris Street, cafeteria sign (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 164c, Mr. Eddie Dorie on stilts, Broadway and Morris Street, cafeteria sign (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 164d, Mr. Eddie Dorie on stilts, Broadway and Morris Street, cafeteria sign (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 164e, Mr. Eddie Dorie on stilts, Broadway and Morris Street, clothes sign (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 165, Group of office workers on roof (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 166a, Alfred Funck and dog, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 166b, Alfred Funck and dog, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 166c, Alfred Funck and dog, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 166l, Alfred Funck and dog, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 166d, Alfred Funck and dog, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 166e, Alfred Funck and dog, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 166f, Alfred Funck's dog, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 166g, Alfred Funck's dog, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 166h, Alfred Funck's dog, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 167a, Miss Juana Engel, seated with balloons (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 167b, Miss Juana Engel, on bench with balloons (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 167c, Miss Juana Engel, standing with balloons (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 167d, Miss Juana Engel, seated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 167e, Miss Juana Engel, standing with hat (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 168, Parade watchers, Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 169, Crowds on dock (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 170a, [Snow scene, man with dogs] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 170b, [cat in yard] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 170c, Frank Ingalls (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 171cc, Three children at river's edge (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 171a, Four children playing instruments (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 171b, Two children dancing (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 172a, US Custom House (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 172b, US Custom House, group posed on steps for photo (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 172c, US Custom House, group posed on steps for photo (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 174a, Boy Scouts (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 174b, New ocean liner passing Battery Park, 1928 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 174c, New ocean liner passing Battery Park, 1928 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 175, Statue of Benjamin DePeyster, Bowling Green (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 176, NY Telephone Building, West and Vesey Street, 1928 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 177, City Hall Park [snow] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 178, American Bank Note Company, Broad Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 179, Temple Emanu-El, 1 East 65th Street at Fifth Avenue (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 181, Dog on stoop (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 182a, Richmond Hill (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 182c, Cotton and Exchange Building, Beaver Street and William Street, 1908 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 182b Richmond Hill (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 183a, Cannon memorial to defenders at McGowns Pass, 1907 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 183b, [statue of lion and cub in grass] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 183c, [statue of lion and cub in grass] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 184, Dorilton Apartment House, Broadway and 71st Street, 1908 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 185, Apartment house, southwest corner of 72nd Street and Riverside Drive, 1908 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 200a, Custom House, Bowling Green, Parker and Davis political banner (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 200b, Custom House under construction, Bowling Green, Parker and Davis (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 200c, Custom House, Bowling Green, Parker and Davis political banner (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 200d, Custom House under construction, Bowling Green (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 200e, Custom House, Bowling Green (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 200f, Custom House, Bowling Green (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 201, Tower of NY Produce Exchange, 2 Broadway, 1905 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 202a, Whitehall Bldg under construction, 1900 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 202c, Whitehall Bldg 17 Battery Place (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 202b, Whitehall Bldg under construction, 1900 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 202d, Whitehall Bldg 17 Battery Place (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 203a, NY Produce Exchange Bank under construction, 10-12 Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 203b, NY Produce Exchange Bank under construction, 10-12 Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 203c, NY Produce Exchange Bank under construction, 10-12 Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 203d, NY Produce Exchange Bank under construction, 10-12 Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 203e, NY Produce Exchange Bank under construction, 10-12 Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 203f, NY Produce Exchange Bank under construction, 10-12 Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 203g, NY Produce Exchange Bank under construction, 10-12 Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 204a, Standard Oil Company building (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 204b, Standard Oil Company building under construction (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 205, Entrance to Trinity building, 111 Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 206, Eden Musee, north side of 23rd Street east of Sixth Avenue (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 207, YMCA, north side of 23rd Street, west of Seventh Avenue (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 208, Knickerbocker Jewelry Company building, Fifth Avenue and 16th Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 209a, Flatiron Building, 23rd Street looking south, United Cigar Stores in cattlecatcher (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 209b, Flatiron Building, 23rd Street looking south through Madison Square Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 209c, Flatiron Building, 23rd Street looking south (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 209d, Flatiron Building, 23rd Street looking south (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 210, New York Times Building under construction, 1903-1904 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 211, Judson Church, Washington Square South (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 212, St. Patrick's Cathedral (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 213, St. Paul's Chapel, Broadway and Vesey Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 214, St. Thomas Church, Fifth Avenue at 53rd Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 215a, St. Nicholas Collegiate Church, 48th Street and Fifth Avenue (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 215b, St. Nicholas Collegiate Church, 48th Street and Fifth Avenue, Fifth Avenue bus (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 215c, St. Nicholas Collegiate Church, 48th Street and Fifth Avenue (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 216a, Elevated Railroad Terminal, South Ferry (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 216b, Elevated Railroad Terminal, South Ferry (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 216c, Elevated Railroad Terminal, South Ferry (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 217a, Elevated railroad, Whitehall and State Streets, 1907 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 217b, Elevated railroad, Whitehall and State Streets, 1907 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 218a, Crowds in Seward Park, East Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 218b, Crowds in Seward Park, East Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 219, Grant's Tomb, Riverside Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 220, Ice skating, Central Park, 1905 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 221a, The Arsenal, Central Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 221a, Toy boat, Central Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 221b, Goat cart, Central Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 223a, Broad Street at Beaver Street looking north, Horse-drawn carts (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 223b, Broad Street at Beaver Street looking north, Horse-drawn carts (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 224, Broad Street looking east on Beaver Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 225, Broad Street at Exchange Place looking south (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 226a, Eighth Avenue and 116th Street, 1907 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 226b, Chambers Street, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 227a, Chambers Street looking west (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 227b, Approach to Brooklyn Bridge looking north [Order of Acorns banner] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 229a, Fifth Avenue north from 9th Street showing Church of Ascension at 10th Street and First Presbyterian Church at 11th Street, horse-drawn bus (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 229b, Fifth Avenue north from 9th Street showing Church of Ascension at 10th Street and First Presbyterian Church at 11th Street, electric bus (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 230, Fifth Avenue in the 30s (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 232a, Parade, Fifth Avenue looking south from around 35th Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 232b, Parade, Fifth Avenue looking south from around 35th Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - 233,Fifth Avenue looking north from 32nd Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
  - Subseries I.2: Uncataloged prints
    - Street scenes (Offsite-box 2)
- Series II. Negatives
  Digital copies of negatives are available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
  - Subseries II.1: Individually cataloged negatives
    - 1e, Aquarium, Battery Park (Box 3)
    - 1f, Aquarium, Battery Park, from above (Box 3)
    - 1g, Aquarium, Battery Park, from above (Box 3)
    - 2a, U.S. Immigration Service building in Battery Park (Box 3)
    - 2b, U.S. Immigration Service building in Battery Park, horse-drawn delivery wagons (Box 3)
    - 4b, Washington Building, 1 Broadway, under construction, Battery Park (Box 3)
    - 5a, Maritime Building, 8-10 Bridge Street (Box 3)
    - 5b, Maritime Building, 8-10 Bridge Street (Box 3)
    - 5c, Maritime Building, 8-10 Bridge Street (Box 3)
    - 5d, Maritime Building, 8-10 Bridge Street (Box 3)
    - 6a, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway, under construction (Box 3)
    - 6b, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway, under construction (Box 3)
    - 6c, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway, under construction (Box 3)
    - 6d, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway, under construction (Box 3)
    - 6e, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway, under construction (Box 3)
    - 6f, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway (Box 3)
    - 6g, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway (Box 3)
    - 6h, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway (Box 3)
    - 7a, 10-12 Broadway, addition to Standard Oil Building, under construction (Box 3)
    - 7b, 10-12 Broadway, addition to Standard Oil Building (Box 3)
    - 8a, Washington Building, 1 Broadway, Battery Park (Box 3)
    - 8b, Washington Building, 1 Broadway, Battery Park, delivery wagon (Box 3)
    - 9, West Street Building, 90 West Street (Box 3)
  - Subseries II.2: Uncataloged negatives
    - Cellulose nitrate film (cold storage) (Box 3-6, 16, Packet 1)
    - Glass plate negatives (Box 7-14)